It's a dangerous world out there in cyberspace.
网络空间是个危险的世界。
Hackers, viruses, and malware, among others, all exist and are very real threats.
黑客、病毒和恶意软件等都是真实存在的威胁。
A 2017 UK government cyber-security breaches survey showed that in the preceding 12 months, just under half of the companies asked had identified an attack or breach. That could have been disastrous.
2017年英国政府网络安全漏洞调查显示，在之前的12个月里，近一半受访公司识别到攻击或漏洞，这可能带来灾难性后果。
The problem is not the computers, firewalls or encryption - it's us.
问题不在于电脑、防火墙或加密技术——而在于我们自己。
People are bad at following good cyber-security protocol – such as using an effective password.
人们不擅长遵守良好的网络安全协议，比如使用有效密码。
We're also pretty dumb when it comes to clicking on links and downloading content we shouldn't, Ian Pratt, co-founder of cyber-security firm Bromium told the BBC.
网络安全公司Bromium联合创始人伊恩・普拉特告诉BBC，我们也很愚蠢地点击不该点的链接和下载不该下的内容。
With that in mind, here are three tips to keep you 'cyber-safe'.
考虑到这一点，以下是三个让你“网络安全”的建议。
Passwords are a weakness.
密码是一个弱点。
The ideal password should be at least eight characters long, and contain upper and lower case letters, symbols and numbers. And don't use a common word such as 'password'.
理想密码至少应8个字符，包含大小写字母、符号和数字，不要用“password”这样的常见词。
"This makes you vulnerable to a scrape attack. This is where hackers take the most common passwords and try them on millions of accounts," Thomas Pedersen from OneLogin, an identity and access management company, told the BBC.
身份和访问管理公司OneLogin的托马斯・佩德森告诉BBC：“这会让你易受‘撒网式密码攻击’，即黑客用最常见密码尝试数百万个账户。”
Keep your equipment up-to-date by installing the latest security updates for your computer - obviously.
显然，要通过安装最新安全更新让设备保持最新状态。
Less obvious perhaps, is doing so for other technology also connected to the internet – such as your router.
但可能被忽视的是，其他联网设备（如路由器）也需如此。
A recent study carried out by the American Consumer Institute Centre for Citizen Research found that "five out of six routers are inadequately updated for known security flaws." These require software updates, too. And don't forget your other smart devices, such as your smart TV!
美国消费者协会公民研究中心最近的研究发现，“六分之五的路由器未针对已知安全漏洞进行充分更新”，这些设备也需要软件更新，别忘了其他智能设备，比如智能电视！
Finally, consider enabling multi-factor authentication for your accounts. That's where a mobile phone or dongle is used to verify access to a device.
最后，考虑为账户启用多因素认证，即使用手机或加密狗验证设备访问权限。
If your password becomes compromised, no access can be obtained without your second authentication device… so don't lose your phone!
如果密码泄露，没有第二个认证设备就无法访问——所以别丢手机！
In the future, biometrics such as voice and fingerprint may make this easier.
未来，语音和指纹等生物识别技术可能让这更简单。
The internet is wonderful, but security threats do exist.
互联网很美好，但安全威胁确实存在。
Fortunately, with a little common sense and forethought, you can be secure from the majority of cyber-security threats.
幸运的是，只要一点常识和先见之明，你就能抵御大多数网络安全威胁。